Never Forget.
Rewind This! is a documentary film directed by Josh Johnson.
Home video changed the world.
The cultural and historical impact of the VHS tape was enormous.
This film traces the ripples of that impact by examining the myriad aspects
of society that were altered by the creation of videotape.
Self, played by Atom Egoyan.
Self, played by Cassandra Peterson.
Self, played by Lloyd Kaufman.
Self, played by Jason Eisener.
Self, played by Mamoru Oshii.
Self, played by Frank Henenlotter.
Rewind is a 2013 made-for-television science fiction film which served
as the pilot episode of an unaired television show.
It premiered in the United States in August 2013.
The film explores themes of pop culture,
collector, vhs, home video, video store.